Guide to the Zelda Fichandler papers, 1950-2000
George Mason University Libraries
- Zelda Fichandler papers
  - poet in residence (Box 130, Folder 3)
  - 1964 draft report on Arena Stage (Box 130, Folder 4)
  - Ford Grants interim report (Box 130, Folder 5)
  - Old Dominion Foundation (Box 130, Folder 6)
  - correspondence: Ford and Old Dominion Foundations (Box 130, Folder 7)
  - Ford Grant for New Building, 1961 (Box 130, Folder 8)
  - grant application materials (Box 130, Folder 9)
  - Rockafeller Report (Box 130, Folder 10)
  - Actors Workshop (Box 131, Folder 1)
  - permanent professional theatre in a large American City (Box 131, Folder 2)
  - attendance sheets (Box 131, Folder 3)
  - correspondence: training program (Box 131, Folder 4)
  - training program (Box 131, Folder 5)
  - correspondence: training program (Box 131, Folder 6)
  - correspondence: staff meetings (Box 131, Folder 7)
  - misc. correspondence (Box 131, Folder 8)
  - correspondence: Training program (Box 131, Folder 9)
  - training program: Rockafeller letter (Box 131, Folder 10)
  - "beauty checkout" (Box 131, Folder 11)
  - Ed's training paper, 1968 (Box 131, Folder 12)
  - Arena Stage Budget info and reseach, 1988 (Box 132, Folder 1)
  - Arena Stage budget and research, 1988-1989 (Box 132, Folder 2)
  - Arena Stage budget and research, 1989 (Box 132, Folder 3)
  - Arena Stage Budget, box office1989 (Box 132, Folder 4)
  - misc. collection of writings (Box 132, Folder 5)
  - National Theatre Award info and guestbook, 1990 (Box 132, Folder 6)
  - correspondence: misc. 1967-1968 (Box 133, Folder 1)
  - information on London trip, 1966 (Box 133, Folder 2)
  - London, May 1965 (Box 133, Folder 3)
  - Athens and London trip, August 1965 (Box 133, Folder 4)
  - London, August 1968 (Box 133, Folder 5)
  - correspondence: German Embassy (Box 133, Folder 6)
  - Athens and London information, 1965 (Box 133, Folder 7)
  - Greek Travel Request (Box 133, Folder 8)
  - London booklets, May 1965 (Box 133, Folder 9)
  - Hong Kong trip, 1979-180 (Box 134, Folder 1)
  - "The Great White Hope", script (Box 134, Folder 2)
  - "The Great White Hope", script (Box 134, Folder 3)
  - "The Great White Hope", script w/ revisions (Box 134, Folder 4)
  - "The Great White Hope", manuscript files (Box 135, Folder 1)
  - "The Great White Hope", non-manuscript files (Box 135, Folder 2)
  - "The Great White Hope", synopsis of scenes (Box 135, Folder 3)
  - "The Great White Hope", manuscript and scene synopsis (Box 135, Folder 4)
  - correspondence: Herman Levin - GWH (Box 136, Folder 1)
  - "Great White Hope", information (Box 136, Folder 2)
  - "Great White Hope", scripts and reviews (Box 136, Folder 3)
  - Requests for GWH scripts (Box 136, Folder 4)
  - "The Great White Hope", correspondence and reviews (Box 136, Folder 5)
  - "Great White Hope", misc. info (Box 136, Folder 6)
  - "Great White Hope", broadway reviews (Box 136, Folder 7)
  - "Great White Hope", newsclippings and misc. info (Box 136, Folder 8)
  - correspondence: Howard Sackler (Box 136, Folder 9)
  - "Enemy of the People", production materials (Box 137, Folder 1)
  - "Enemy of the People", script with revisions (Box 137, Folder 2)
  - "Enemy of the People", John Patrick Vincent version (Box 137, Folder 3)
  - "An Enemy of the People", reviews and program (Box 137, Folder 4)
  - "An Enemy of the People", transcript (Box 137, Folder 5)
  - "Enemy of the People", acting script (Box 137, Folder 6)
  - The English mystery plays (Box 137, Folder 7)
  - "Execution of Justice", playbill, review and misc. information (Box 138, Folder 1)
  - "Execution of Justice", script and research materials (Box 138, Folder 2)
  - "Execution of Private Slovak", correspondence (Box 138, Folder 3)
  - "Exit the King", correspondence (Box 138, Folder 4)
  - "Exquisite Torture", playbill (Box 138, Folder 5)
  - "Extremities", playbill (Box 138, Folder 6)
  - "The Fabulous Miss Manc", playbill (Box 138, Folder 7)
  - "Faces of Love", correspondence (Box 138, Folder 8)
  - "Family Business", playbill and correspondence (Box 138, Folder 9)
  - "Family Devotions", playbill (Box 138, Folder 10)
  - "Family Reunion", correspondence (Box 138, Folder 11)
  - "The Farm", correspondence (Box 138, Folder 12)
  - "Father was a Particular Man", review (Box 138, Folder 13)
  - "Federal Theatre Project", articles (Box 138, Folder 14)
  - "Fefu and her friends", correspondence (Box 138, Folder 15)
  - "Feiffer's America", reviews (Box 138, Folder 16)
  - "Felix", correspondence (Box 138, Folder 17)
  - "Fen", review (Box 138, Folder 18)
  - "Fences", reviews and other info (Box 139, Folder 1)
  - "The Fetishist", script (Box 139, Folder 2)
  - "The Fifth of July", review (Box 139, Folder 3)
  - "Figaro Gets a Divorce", correspondence (Box 139, Folder 4)
  - "Filial Pieties", script (Box 139, Folder 5)
  - "Filumera", playbill (Box 139, Folder 6)
  - "Final Curtain", playbill (Box 139, Folder 7)
  - "The Fireman's Flame", correspondence (Box 139, Folder 8)
  - "The First Breeze of Summer", correspondence (Box 139, Folder 9)
  - "The First of April", playbill (Box 139, Folder 10)
  - "First The Good News", correspondence and reviews (Box 139, Folder 11)
  - "Fishing", playbill (Box 139, Folder 12)
  - "Five on the BAck Hand Side", review (Box 139, Folder 13)
  - "Five of Us", script (Box 139, Folder 14)
  - "Enrico IV", correspondence, casting info and misc. materials (Box 140, Folder 1)
  - "Enrico IV", misc. production materials (Box 140, Folder 2)
  - "Enrico IV", misc. production materials (Box 140, Folder 3)
  - "Enrico", historical background (Box 140, Folder 4)
  - "Enrico", playbill and correspondence (Box 140, Folder 5)
  - "Entertaining Mr. Sloane", playbill and correspondence (Box 140, Folder 6)
  - "Entertaining Strangers", playbill (Box 140, Folder 7)
  - "Episode", correspondence (Box 140, Folder 8)
  - "Equus", playbill and review (Box 140, Folder 9)
  - "Escurial", review (Box 140, Folder 10)
  - "Esker Mike and his Wife", press release (Box 140, Folder 11)
  - "Evelyn Brown", program and info (Box 140, Folder 12)
  - "An Evening at Widow Begick's", program and correspondence (Box 140, Folder 13)
  - "An Evenings Frost", correspondence (Box 140, Folder 14)
  - "Every Good Boy Does Fine", playbill (Box 140, Folder 15)
  - "Everything in the Garden", correspondence (Box 140, Folder 16)
  - "Evita", program (Box 140, Folder 17)
  - "The Exception and the Rule", review (Box 140, Folder 18)
  - "Execution of Justice", review (Box 140, Folder 19)
  - remarks: Cultural Alliance of Greater Washington Gala and Reception, 1990 (Box 141, Folder 1)
  - testimony: Congressional Appropriations Committee, 1990 (Box 141, Folder 2)
  - NEA funding information (Box 141, Folder 3)
  - testimony: Congressional Appropriations Committee (NEA), 1991 (Box 141, Folder 4)
  - interview: Museum and Arts magazine, 1990 (Box 141, Folder 5)
  - written material for 40th anniversary (Box 141, Folder 6)
  - remarks: 1st rehearsal of "Caucasion Chalk Circle" (Box 141, Folder 7)
  - interview: Voice of America, 1990 (with audio cassette) (Box 141, Folder 8)
  - remarks: board meeting, 1990 (Box 141, Folder 9)
  - speech: 1990 Arena Stage Gala (Box 141, Folder 10)
  - materials relating to the 40th anniversary (Box 141, Folder 11)
  - remarks: long range planning committee, 1987 (Box 142, Folder 1)
  - remarks: Leon Scioscia's good-bye party, 1987 (Box 142, Folder 2)
  - remarks: Leslie Cass memorial service, 1987 (Box 142, Folder 3)
  - remarks: introductions of Llyod Richard (Box 142, Folder 4)
  - remarks: reception for Llyod Richards and August Wilson, 1987 (Box 142, Folder 5)
  - remarks: thoughts on non-traditional casting, 1987 (Box 142, Folder 6)
  - remarks: 1st rehearsal of "Enrico IV" (Box 142, Folder 7)
  - Artistic Statement, 1987 (Box 142, Folder 8)
  - remarks: farwell party for James C. Nicola, 1988 (Box 142, Folder 9)
  - remarks: board meeting, June 1988 (Box 142, Folder 10)
  - correspondence: Ford Foundation Women's program (Box 142, Folder 11)
  - interview: NPR, 1988 (Box 142, Folder 12)
  - remarks: All Theatre Meetings, 1988 (Box 142, Folder 13)
  - remarks: executive committee meeting, re: 1988-1989 budget (Box 142, Folder 14)
  - correspondence: NYU (Box 143, Folder 1)
  - correspondence: NYU (Box 143, Folder 2)
  - interview: Museum and Arts magazine, Oct. 1990 (Box 143, Folder 3)
  - remarks and information: Center Theatre Group, Board of Directors, 1990 (Box 143, Folder 4)
  - remarks: Historical Society of Washington DC, Nov. 1990 (Box 143, Folder 5)
  - Articstic Directors Statement, 1990 (Box 143, Folder 6)
  - Lee Reynolds Award, Dec. 1990 (Box 143, Folder 7)
  - "Caucasian Chalk Circle", criticisim and response (Box 143, Folder 8)
  - remarks: 1st rehearsal, "Born Guilty" and "Before it Hits Home", Dec. 1990 (Box 143, Folder 9)
  - remarks: Stephen Wade Anniversary Party, Jan. 1991 (Box 143, Folder 10)
  - remarks: Trailblazer award by Othro Pharmaceutical Corp., 1991 (Box 143, Folder 11)
  - remarks: all staff meeting, Sept. 1988 (Box 144, Folder 1)
  - correspondence: Richard Corniff, Aug. 1988 (Box 144, Folder 2)
  - Artistic Statement, 1988-1989 (Box 144, Folder 3)
  - remarks: Cosmos Club, "The Dramatic Imagination", March 1989 (Box 144, Folder 4)
  - interview: The Directors Voice: Twenty One Interviews (Box 144, Folder 5)
  - remarks: 1st rehersal "On The Town", and related correspondence (Box 144, Folder 6)
  - remarks and material: Cultural Alliance of Greater Washington Founders Award Honors, 1989 (Box 144, Folder 7)
  - misc. materials: 1989 trip to Russia (Box 144, Folder 8)
  - misc. materials: 1989 trip to Russia (Box 144, Folder 9)
  - remarks: 'Cultural Diversity', Department Heads Meeting, May 1989 (Box 144, Folder 10)
  - remarks: stratigic planning committee, May 1989 (Box 144, Folder 11)
  - remarks: workshop library on world humor, May 1989 (Box 144, Folder 12)
  - Stratford Canada Shakespear Festival, brochures and info (Box 145, Folder 1)
  - correspondence: Roger Straus (Box 145, Folder 2)
  - memorial service info: Sheppard Strudwick (Box 145, Folder 3)
  - correspondence: The Support Center (Box 145, Folder 4)
  - remarks: David Susskind Show (Box 145, Folder 5)
  - correspondence: Dolores Sutton (Box 145, Folder 6)
  - Suzuki Project (Box 145, Folder 7)
  - correspondence: Jeff Sweet (Box 145, Folder 8)
  - correspondence: Fontaine Syer (Box 145, Folder 9)
  - correspondence: Oleg Tabakov (Box 145, Folder 10)
  - correspondence: Dennis Tate (Box 145, Folder 11)
  - tax letter for actors, 1979 (Box 145, Folder 12)
  - correspondence: Willa Taylor (Box 145, Folder 13)
  - correspondence: Teatro Libre (Box 145, Folder 14)
  - correspondence: Jessica Teich (Box 145, Folder 15)
  - Arena Stage on Television, correspondence and information (Box 145, Folder 16)
  - correspondence: Margott Del Tenney (Box 145, Folder 17)
  - Theatre in DC information (Box 145, Folder 18)
  - correspondence: Theatre Co. of Boston (Box 145, Folder 19)
  - correspondence: Theatre Development Fund (Box 145, Folder 20)
  - remarks and materials: 1976 Theatre Communication Group meeting (Box 145, Folder 21)
  - Arena Stage Annual Report, 1988-1989 (Box 146, Folder 1)
  - press releases, 1989 (Box 146, Folder 2)
  - remarks: NYU (Box 146, Folder 3)
  - remarks: press confrence, Glass Managerie (Box 146, Folder 4)
  - news clippings, Sunday Post, Oct. 8, 1989 (Box 146, Folder 5)
  - remarks and correspondence: Theatre Trustees of America, 1989 (Box 146, Folder 6)
  - remarks: Birthday of Rose Robinson Cowen, Nov. 2, 1989 (Box 146, Folder 7)
  - atristic statement, 1990 (Box 146, Folder 8)
  - Sidney Yates folder (Box 146, Folder 9)
  - NEA grant 1989 (Box 146, Folder 10)
  - news clippings, Nov. 1989 (Box 146, Folder 11)
  - remarks: 1st rehersal "Doll House", Jan. 1990 (Box 146, Folder 12)
  - correspondence: Don Corathers (Box 146, Folder 13)
  - correspondence: Peter Zeisler (Box 147, Folder 1)
  - correspondence: Theatre Communications Group (Box 147, Folder 2)
  - correspondence: Lori Berhon (Box 147, Folder 3)
  - memo: Theatre Communication Group, 1982 (Box 147, Folder 4)
  - Theatre Communications Group translation forum material, 1984 (Box 147, Folder 5)
  - correspondence: Theatre Communications Group (Box 147, Folder 6)
  - correspondence: Theatre Communications Group (Box 147, Folder 8)
  - remarks: Theatre Communications Group conference, June 1978 (Box 147, Folder 9)
  - Theatre Communications Group information (Box 147, Folder 10)
  - Theatre Communications Group, chicago 1989 (Box 147, Folder 11)
  - "Storm King", correspondence (Box 147, Folder 12)
  - Theatre Communications Group directories (Box 147, Folder 13)
  - correspondence: Al Miller (Box 148, Folder 1)
  - correspondence: Meyer Foundation (Box 148, Folder 2)
  - correspondence: Eve Merriam (Box 148, Folder 3)
  - misc. memos (Box 148, Folder 4)
  - Mellon Foundation grant application, 1979 (Box 148, Folder 5)
  - correspondence: Mellon Foundation (Box 148, Folder 6)
  - correspondence: Gunter Meisner (Box 148, Folder 7)
  - correspondence: Charles Mee (Box 148, Folder 8)
  - correspondence: Lynn Meadow (Box 148, Folder 9)
  - correspondence: John McQuiggan (Box 148, Folder 10)
  - correspondence: Pat McHrath (Box 148, Folder 11)
  - correspondence: Heather McDonald (Box 148, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence: John Mazzola (Box 148, Folder 13)
  - Mayor's Art Award, 1981program and article (Box 148, Folder 14)
  - correspondence: Ruth Mayleas, NEA (Box 148, Folder 15)
  - correspondence and information: Theatre de Complicite (Box 149, Folder 1)
  - Theatre Information Bulletins and the Theatrical Index (Box 149, Folder 2)
  - Theatre Exchange International: articles and correspondence (Box 149, Folder 3)
  - correspondence: Theatre Crafts Magazine (Box 149, Folder 4)
  - Theatre Trustees of America: information, articles, brochures (Box 149, Folder 5)
  - Tazewell Thompson (actor): professional information (Box 149, Folder 6)
  - correspondence: Joan Vail Thome (Box 149, Folder 7)
  - correspondence: Rosemarie Tickler (Box 149, Folder 8)
  - Ticket price information, 1990-1991 season (Box 149, Folder 9)
  - Laurence Tisch: article and correspondence, 1986 (Box 149, Folder 10)
  - correspondence and resume: Bob Tolan (Box 149, Folder 11)
  - Lily Tomlin: playbill (Box 149, Folder 12)
  - correspondence: Paul A. Mayer (Box 150, Folder 1)
  - correspondence: Joan Maxwell (Box 150, Folder 2)
  - correspondence: Ada Brown Mather (Box 150, Folder 3)
  - correspondence: Larry Maslon (Box 150, Folder 4)
  - correspondence: Ed Martenson (Box 150, Folder 5)
  - correspondence: Mary Baldwin College (Box 150, Folder 6)
  - correspondence: Luis Martinez (Box 150, Folder 7)
  - correspondence: Jeanne Marshall (Box 150, Folder 8)
  - correspondence: Edith Markson (Box 150, Folder 9)
  - correspondence: Edie Markson (Box 150, Folder 10)
  - correspondence: Brian Marcus (Box 150, Folder 11)
  - correspondence: Gerard Manninp (Box 150, Folder 12)
  - correspondence: The Market Theatre (Box 150, Folder 13)
  - correspondence: Paul Mann (Box 150, Folder 14)
  - correspondence: Emily Mann (Box 150, Folder 15)
  - "After the Fall," Misc Production notes (Box 151, Folder 1)
  - "After the Fall," Photos, News clippings, Misc. production notes (Box 151, Folder 2)
  - "After the Fall," Scripts with annotations (Box 151, Folder 3)
  - "After the Fall," Scripts, News Articles, Notes, One book "Scoundrel Time" (Box 151, Folder 4)
  - "After the Fall," Playbills and program (Box 151, Folder 5)
  - "After the Fall," Script, Rehearsal remarks, Misc. notes (Box 151, Folder 6)
  - "After the Fall," Script (Box 151, Folder 7)
  - "Animal Crackers," Misc. production notes (Box 152, Folder 1)
  - "Animal Crackers," Playbills, Programs, News Articles (Box 152, Folder 2)
  - "The Animal Kingdom," News articles (Box 152, Folder 3)
  - "Anteroom," Script (Box 152, Folder 4)
  - "Ashes," Playbills, Correspondense, News articles (Box 152, Folder 5)
  - "As Is," Playbill (Box 152, Folder 6)
  - "As it is in Heaven," Correspondense, News articles (Box 152, Folder 7)
  - "Assasination 1865," Correspondense (Box 152, Folder 8)
  - "Assasins," Announcement (Box 152, Folder 9)
  - "As You Like It," News articles, Playbill, Misc. notes (Box 152, Folder 10)
  - "Aunt Dan and Lemon," Playbill, News release (Box 152, Folder 11)
  - "The Autumn Garden," Playbills, News articles, Misc. Notes (Box 152, Folder 12)
  - "Avner the Eccentric," Photo, Correspondense, News articles (Box 152, Folder 13)
  - "Before It Hits Home," Photo, Announcements, Playbill, Correspondense, News articles (Box 152, Folder 14)
  - "Abyssinia," Playbill, News Articles (Box 153, Folder 1)
  - "Accidental Death of an Anarchist," Scripts, Correspondense, News articles (Box 153, Folder 2)
  - "Accidental Death of an Anarchist," Correspondense, News articles, Partial script (Box 153, Folder 3)
  - "AC/DC," Letter, Article (Box 153, Folder 4)
  - "Adaptation/Next," Playbill, Correspondense (Box 153, Folder 5)
  - "After My Own Heart," Playbill (Box 153, Folder 6)
  - "Agnes of God," Stagebill (Box 153, Folder 7)
    unfastened, loose pages
  - "Ah, Wilderness!," Correspondense, Program, News articles, Misc. notes (Box 153, Folder 8)
  - "Ain't Misbehavin'," Playbill, News articles, Announcement (Box 153, Folder 9)
  - "Ain't Supposed to Die a Natural Death," Playbill, News articles, Letter (Box 153, Folder 10)
    Playbill unfastened, loose pages
  - "All My Songs," Magazine (Box 153, Folder 11)
  - "All Over," Playbill, News article, Letter (Box 153, Folder 12)
  - "All the Way Home," Magazine article (Box 153, Folder 13)
  - "All's Well That Ends Well," News articles (Box 153, Folder 14)
  - "Alpha Beta," Misc. notes, News articles, Correspondense (Box 153, Folder 15)
  - "Alphabetical Order," News article (Box 153, Folder 16)
  - "Amazing Grace," News articles (Box 153, Folder 17)
  - "Amen Corner," Correspondense (Box 153, Folder 18)
  - "American Buffalo," Script, Correspondense, Notes, News articles (Box 153, Folder 19)
  - "The American Clock," News article (Box 153, Folder 20)
  - "American Days," News articles (Box 153, Folder 21)
  - "America Hurrah," Playbill (Box 153, Folder 22)
    unfastend, loose pages
  - "An American Tragedy," Misc. Production notes (Box 153, Folder 23)
  - "Amerika," Program, Correspondense (Box 153, Folder 24)
  - "An American Journey," Playbill, Program (Box 153, Folder 25)
  - correspondence: Margaret Lynn (Box 154, Folder 1)
  - correspondence: geraldine lust (Box 154, Folder 2)
  - correspondence: Bill Luers (Box 154, Folder 3)
  - correspondence: W. McNeil Lowry (Box 154, Folder 4)
  - correspondence: W. McNeil Lowry (Box 154, Folder 5)
  - LORT subcommittee: non-profit comerical theatre (Box 154, Folder 6)
  - correspondence: Papp Lincoln Center (Box 154, Folder 7)
  - Lincoln Center Crisis, 1973 (Box 154, Folder 8)
  - Long Warf tour, 1979 (Box 154, Folder 9)
  - LORT (Box 154, Folder 10)
  - Manhattan Rythm Kings (Box 155, Folder 1)
  - Manhattan Theatre Club: article, 1990 (Box 155, Folder 2)
  - correspondence: Ed Mangum (Box 155, Folder 3)
  - correspondence: Loring Mandel (Box 155, Folder 4)
  - correspondence: David Marnet (Box 155, Folder 5)
  - correspondence: MacArthur Foundation (Box 155, Folder 6)
  - correspondence: Maharishi College of Natural Law (Box 155, Folder 7)
  - correspondence: Mabow Mines (Box 155, Folder 8)
  - Mr. Lyubimov, Russian Director (1 of 4) (Box 155, Folder 9)
  - Mr. Lyubimov, Russian Director (2 of 4) (Box 155, Folder 10)
  - Mr. Lyubimov, Russian Director (3 of 4) (Box 155, Folder 11)
  - Mr. Lyubimov, Russian Director (4 of 4) (Box 155, Folder 12)
  - "The Good Person of Setzuan", playbill and background material (Box 156, Folder 1)
  - "The Good Person of Setzuan", background and research information (Box 156, Folder 2)
  - "The Good Times are Killing Me", playbill (Box 156, Folder 3)
  - "Goose-Goose and Tom David Rabe", background information (Box 156, Folder 4)
  - "M. Gorky", program and info (Box 156, Folder 5)
  - "GORKY", correspondence and info (Box 156, Folder 6)
  - "Gospel at Colonus", script and research (Box 156, Folder 7)
  - "Government Man", correspondence (Box 156, Folder 8)
  - "G.R. Point", correspondence (Box 156, Folder 9)
  - "The Grand Kabuk", playbill (Box 156, Folder 10)
  - "Grease", playbill (Box 156, Folder 11)
  - "The Great Magoo", correspondence (Box 156, Folder 12)
  - "The Great Macdaddy", photos, reviews and correspondence (Box 156, Folder 13)
  - "The Grapes of Wrath", playbill (Box 156, Folder 14)
  - "Greater Tuna", reviews etc. (Box 156, Folder 15)
  - "Gramma", notes (Box 156, Folder 16)
  - "Guys and Dolls", playbill and correspondence (Box 157, Folder 1)
  - "Grotowski", research (Box 157, Folder 2)
  - "Green Card", playbill (Box 157, Folder 3)
  - "Greek Plays", correspondence (Box 157, Folder 4)
  - "The Great White Hope", script (Box 157, Folder 5)
  - "The Great White Hope", reviews, programs, playbills, misc. materials (Box 157, Folder 6)
  - "Hamlet", notes and correspondence (Box 157, Folder 7)
  - "Gyubal - Witkiewicz", correspondence and background (Box 157, Folder 8)
  - "Hagar's Children", reviews and correspondence (Box 157, Folder 9)
  - "Hamletmachine", background (Box 157, Folder 10)
  - "Handle with Care", reviews (Box 157, Folder 11)
  - "Happy Birthday, Wanda June", playbill (Box 157, Folder 12)
  - "Happy Days", playbill (Box 157, Folder 13)
  - "Happy End", script, misc. materials (Box 157, Folder 14)
  - "Hark", program (Box 157, Folder 15)
  - "Harry Chapin: Lies and Legends", correspondence (Box 158, Folder 1)
  - "Harry Outside", reviews and correspondence (Box 158, Folder 2)
  - "Harry Ruby's Songs My Mother Never Sang", playbill and notes (Box 158, Folder 3)
  - "The Hasty Heart", playbill and notes (Box 158, Folder 4)
  - "The Headhunters", playbill (Box 158, Folder 5)
  - "Heartbreak House", script, playbill, review and notes (Box 158, Folder 6)
  - "Heartbreak House", literature materials (Box 158, Folder 7)
  - "Hedda Gabler", playbill, reviews, etc. (Box 158, Folder 8)
  - "Hemingway", correspondence (Box 158, Folder 9)
  - "Henry IV", plahbill and review (Box 158, Folder 10)
  - "Henry V", playbills (Box 158, Folder 11)
  - "Henry VI", correspondence (Box 158, Folder 12)
  - "Flesh, Flash and Frank Harris", program (Box 159, Folder 1)
  - "The Flowering Peach", note (Box 159, Folder 2)
  - "The Flying Karamozov Brothers", stage manager reports (Box 159, Folder 3)
  - "The Fool", review (Box 159, Folder 4)
  - "Foolsfire", invitation (Box 159, Folder 5)
  - "Fool for Love", reviews (Box 159, Folder 6)
  - "Fools Play", correspondence (Box 159, Folder 7)
  - "The Fool Show", reviews (Box 159, Folder 8)
  - "For Colored Grils who have Considered Suicide", reviews (Box 159, Folder 9)
  - "Forbidden Broadway", program (Box 159, Folder 10)
  - "The Foreigner", reviews (Box 159, Folder 11)
  - "Forever Yours Marie-Lou", research and background materials (Box 159, Folder 12)
  - "For the use of the Hall", program and correspondence (Box 159, Folder 13)
  - "The Forest", review (Box 159, Folder 14)
  - "Forget-Me-Not Lane", program and correspondence (Box 159, Folder 15)
  - "Found a Peanut", program (Box 159, Folder 16)
  - "The Forsome",program and correspondence (Box 159, Folder 17)
  - "Four Years After the Revolution"Songs by R. Peasiee", program (Box 159, Folder 18)
  - "The Fox", notes (Box 159, Folder 19)
  - "Fragments of a Trilogy", review (Box 159, Folder 20)
  - "Fragments and other Schisgal Plays", correspondence (Box 159, Folder 21)
  - "The Freeway", playbill (Box 159, Folder 22)
  - "French Without Tears", review (Box 159, Folder 23)
  - "Friends", correspondence (Box 159, Folder 24)
  - "From the Missippi Delta", correspondence and review (Box 159, Folder 25)